airfaresflights.com.au 2013-08-06

# Airfares Flights Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy**

AirfaresFlights.com.au is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following statement to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the AirfaresFlights.com.au Web site. 

If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at;

. 

** Gathering of Information**

AirfaresFlights.com.au does not collect personally identifying information about any individual except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, we may ask you for information when you register for our newsletter or signup to our site services. You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the AirfaresFlights.com.au Web site, but you may be unable to access certain options and services. 

** Cookies **

A cookie is a data file that certain Web sites write to your computer's hard drive when you visit such sites. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user identification code, that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. AirfaresFlights.com.au only uses cookies to improve user experience, this can include through user login sessions and forum postings.

** Browser Level Information **

AirfaresFlights.com.au Web servers automatically collect information about a site user's IP address, browser type and referrer by reading this information from the user's browser (information provided by every user's browser). This information is collected in a database and used--in an aggregated, anonymous manner--in our internal analysis of traffic patterns within our Web site. This information is automatically logged by most Web sites. 

** Use of Information **

Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our Web site. We achieve this goal by, among other things, providing interactive communications such as our electronic newsletters to the e-mail address that you provide to us, and developing future editorial content based on your interests. To develop content targeted to your interests, we use aggregated user information to determine which areas of our Web site users prefer based upon traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but instead how well each page or content area performs overall. 

When you are on an area of AirfaresFlights.com.au and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with AirfaresFlights.com.au as well as business partners and vendors providing hosting and other services for AirfaresFlights.com.au. If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of your information by not using that particular service. These parties, as well as advertisers who contract directly with a third-party service to serve their advertisements, may set their own cookies. 

However, it should be noted that AirfaresFlights.com.au does not, and will not share any personally identifiable information with advertisers that is provided by the user as part of the 'hot deals newsletter' or 'refer a friend' forms.

Please be aware that AirfaresFlights.com.au sponsors, advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those parties and Web sites linked to AirfaresFlights.com.au are not covered by this privacy statement. AirfaresFlights.com.au users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others. 

If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at;

. 

This statement may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.
